{
    "id": "3f9200a37ab74992a0c8c4c9bb79d803",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He promised that he would help me but let me ………………… as usual.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "down",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "472038d0a1324a90a2e12d8340abd660"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will let you …………………. a secret. Mary is seeing a friend of mine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "into",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6e2d05de6f914637ace7b3fa0f49bb94"
        },
        {
            "question": "He might ask but don’t let …………………. that you know where John is.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "on",
                "into"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fd034b9f2fb24ba9b7fe666eec8d0cb9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She refused to let me …………………. the house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "on to",
                "into"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6fc86d88c8e64d6cae1a7b75178251a1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He let ................................................. a big scream when his cut his finger.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "87cd720badad4a56bbe3062e4d840c49"
        },
        {
            "question": "Thanks to his good conduct, he was let ............................................... jail three years early.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "out of",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "24e91e7efcc544cbae76f56f4fe0475d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t know what I was letting myself .......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in for",
                "down",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1e4b500975e74aa49d3d19b4229f1346"
        },
        {
            "question": "As I had lost my keys, I couldn’t let myself ………………… my flat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "on to",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bd5483dbac97421e9f9280b5026efc2b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He thought he would be let ………………… but the judge sent him to jail.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "14eb34368aec4f91b0689d7f1e4fe763"
        },
        {
            "question": "The rain didn’t let .......................................... all day we couldn’t even go for a walk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "up",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e2163fe71a4841d8bfb0af2fb0e4e841"
        }
    ]
}